weeklyworldnews.com 2002-12-03

# Weekly World News

| 

Internet user privacy is of paramount importance to The Weekly World News and our partners. The success of our business depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. Below is information regarding The Weekly World News's commitment to protect the privacy of users and to ensure the integrity of the Internet. 

**Information Collected in Ad Delivery**  
In the course of delivering an ad to you, The Weekly World News and DoubleClick, it's advertising partner, does not collect any personally-identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. The Weekly World News does, however, collect non-personally identifiable information about you, such as the server your computer is logged onto, your browser type (for example, Netscape or Internet Explorer), and whether you responded to the ad delivered. 

The non-personally identifiable information collected by The Weekly World News is used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of The Weekly World News's advertisers. 

There are also other cases when a user voluntarily provides personal information in response to an ad (a survey or purchase form, for example). In these situations, DoubleClick (or a third party engaged by DoubleClick) collects the information on behalf of the advertiser and/or Web site. This information is used by the advertiser and/or The Weekly World News Web Site so that you can receive the goods, services or information that you requested. Where indicated, The Weekly World News may use this information in aggregate form to get a better general understanding of the type of individuals viewing ads on the Web Site. Unless specifically disclosed, the personally-identifiable information collected by The Weekly World News in these cases is not used to deliver personally-tailored ads to a user and is not linked by The Weekly World News to any other information. 

**Sweepstakes**  
When you enter a Weekly World News sweepstakes, the information you provide is not be shared with any third party, unless you agree by checking the opt-in box on the sweepstakes entry form. If you enter a sweepstakes, you agree that the sweepstakes sponsor may use your name in relation to announcing and promoting the winners of the sweepstakes. See the official rules of the sweepstakes you are entering for additional information. 

The Weekly World News does collect aggregate, anonymous information about the sweepstakes. That information is primarily used to help sweepstakes managers choose prizes and make other decisions regarding the organization of the sweepstakes. The Weekly World News does not associate information provided through the sweepstakes with your other web browsing activities or clickstream data. 

**Information Collected by The Weekly World News's Web Site**  
The Weekly World News Web may ask for and collect personally-identifiable information. The Weekly World News is committed to providing meaningful notice and choice to users before any personally-identifiable information is submitted to us. Specifically, users will be informed about how The Weekly World News may use such information, including whether it will be shared with marketing partners or combined with other information available to us. In most cases, the information provided by a user will be contributed a database to enable personally-tailored ad delivery online. Users will always be offered the choice not to provide personally-identifiable information or to have it shared with others. 

**Policy for Children Under the Age of 13**  
AMI sites are not intended for use by children. Children should not provide any personal information or use AMI's public areas, forums, and chats. AMI sites do not accept registrations or collect personally identifiable information from children due to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). [ COPPA](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/kidsprivacy.htm) was enacted to prevent websites from collecting and/or distributing information from children without their parents' consent. For more information on [ COPPA](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/online/kidsprivacy.htm), please refer to the [Federal Trade Commission](http://www.ftc.gov/) Website. 

**Access**  
The Weekly World News offers users who have voluntarily provided personally-identifiable information to The Weekly World News the opportunity to review the information provided and to correct any errors. 

**Cookies**  
The Weekly World News, along with thousands of other Web sites, uses cookies to enhance your Web viewing experience. The Weekly World News's cookies do not damage your system or files in any way. 

Here's how it works. When you are first served an ad through The Weekly World News, our advertising partner, DoubleClick, assigns you a unique number and records that number in the cookie file of your computer. Then, when you visit another site where DoubleClick serves ads, DoubleClick reads this number to help target ads to you. DoubleClick may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services of interest to you. The cookie can help ensure that you do not see the same ad over and over again. Cookies can also help advertisers measure how you utilize an advertiser's site. This information helps our advertisers cater their ads to your needs. 

While we believe that cookies enhance your Web experience by limiting the repetitiveness of advertising and increasing the level of relevant content on the Web, they are not essential for us to continue our leadership position in Web advertising. 

You may opt out of receiving DoubleClick-based cookies by following the link in the next paragraph. Your opt-out will be effective for the entire life of your browser or until you delete the cookie file on your hard drive. In each of these instances, you will appear as a new user to The Weekly World News. Unless you deny The Weekly World News cookie again, The Weekly World News's ad server will deliver a new cookie to your browser. 

If you would like more information on how to opt-out, please [click here](http://www.sonar.com/naiprivacy). 

**Disclosure**  
The Weekly World News makes available all of our information practices at ../neo/privacy.html including in-depth descriptions of our targeting capabilities, our privacy policy, and full disclosure on the use of cookies. In addition, we provide all users with the option to contact us at letters@weeklyworldnews.com  with any further questions or concerns. 

**Security**  
The Weekly World News will maintain the confidentiality of the information that it collects during the process of delivering an ad. The Weekly World News maintains internal practices that help to protect the security and confidentiality of this information by limiting employee access to and use of this information. 

**Industry Efforts to Protect Consumer Privacy**  
For more information about protecting your privacy online, we recommend that you visit [www.nai.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) , [www.netcoalition.com](http://www.netcoalition.com/) , and [www.privacyalliance.org](http://www.privacyalliance.org/) . We also recommend that you review this Privacy Statement periodically, as The Weekly World News may update it from time to time. 

|  |   
---|---|---
